https://www.gamesforfun.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
1. To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
2. To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits.We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.This policy was last modified on 02/06/15Phone: 909.885.3604Hours: Monday – Saturday 9:00am – 5:30pm Closed SundayAddress: 895 W. Rialto Ave., San Bernardino, California 92410Email: sales@gamesforfun.com
We want to talk to you! Please fill out our contact us form with questions.
Learn More!
CONNECT WITH US!
Phone: 909.885.3604Hours: Monday – Saturday 9am – 5pmAddress: 895 W. Rialto Ave., San Bernardino, California 92410Email: sales@gamesforfun.com
© 2020 Games For Fun |Design by Creative 7 designs Inc. | Terms of Service | Privacy Policy | Contact Us | Accessibility Policy
